{
"question": "暑い",
"answer": "あつい"
},
{
"question": "遊ぶ",
"answer": "あそぶ"
},
{
"question": "然し",
"answer": "しかし"
},
{
"question": "無くす",
"answer": "なくす"
},
{
"question": "色々",
"answer": "いろいろ"
},
{
"question": "渡る",
"answer": "わたる"
},
{
"question": "暗い",
"answer": "くらい"
},
{
"question": "此方",
"answer": "こちら"
},
{
"question": "重い",
"answer": "おもい"
},
{
"question": "今晩",
"answer": "こんばん"
},
{
"question": "美味しい",
"answer": "おいしい"
},
{
"question": "消す",
"answer": "けす"
},
{
"question": "易しい",
"answer": "やさしい"
},
{
"question": "閉める",
"answer": "しめる"
},
{
"question": "安い",
"answer": "やすい"
},
{
"question": "遠い",
"answer": "とおい"
},
{
"question": "短い",
"answer": "みじかい"
},
{
"question": "晴れる",
"answer": "はれる"
},
{
"question": "曲がる",
"answer": "まがる"
},
{
"question": "消える",
"answer": "きえる"
},
